Driver Version: 25.20.100.6847
 
Release Version: Production Version

Operating System(s):   

	Microsoft Windows* 10-64 (19H1)

Platforms:

	Ice Lake

		
Release Date: June 21, 2019

CONTENTS

I.	Product Support
II.	Installation Information
III.	Disclaimer

I.  Product Support

Supports Intel(R) UHD Graphics, Intel(R) HD Graphics, Intel(R) Iris(R) Plus Graphics on:

	Ice Lake
	
			
II.  Installation Information      

This document makes references to products developed by Intel. There are some restrictions on how these products may be used, and what information may be disclosed to others. Please read the Disclaimer section and contact your Intel field representative if you would like more information.

III.  Disclaimer

Intel is making no claims of usability, efficacy or warranty. The INTEL SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT contained herein completely defines the license and use of this software.

This document contains information on products in the design phase of development. The information here is subject to change without notice. Do not finalize a design with this information.

*Other names and brands may be claimed as the property of others.
